<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Free | Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/categories/free/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-17T11:13:40-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club Nintendo Rewards]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/02/03/club-nintendo-rewards/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-03T07:03:02-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/02/03/club-nintendo-rewards</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/2-3-2015/rewards.png" title="Club Nintendo Physical Rewards" >
Nintendo&rsquo;s popular loyalty program will be shutting down later this year to make room for something new (I&rsquo;m excited to find out what it will be like). To help current members spend their unused coins, a bunch of new rewards have been put up on the site, both physical and digital ones. <!-- more --></p>

<p>Yesterday, Club Nintendo put up a good amount of new rewards. Some of the top new physical rewards to grab are Animal Crossing Mini Playing Cards (600), a 3DS XL Pouch: The Legend of Zelda (600), a Super Smash Bros. 3 Poster Set v2 (700), a retro Mario T-shirt (700), a Limited Edition 2013 Platinum Poster Set consisting of Luigi, Zelda Wind Waker, and Pikmin posters (700), the first version of the Super Smash Bros 3 Poster Set (700), a Fierce Deity Link Jigsaw Puzzle (800), and a Legend of Zelda: Majora&rsquo;s Mask 3D Messenger Bag (800).</p>

<p>For Club Nintendo, those are some pretty nice physical rewards to end the program with. But Nintendo also put up a huge offering of digital games as well. The list is huge, so I won&rsquo;t mention them all, but a lot of their greatest games can be bought there. Some examples are Super Metroid, EarthBound, many Mario games, The Wonderful 101, Wii Fit U, some great Zelda games, Super Smash Bros., Kid Icarus, Punch-out, Donkey Kong, and a lot more that are both old and new.</p>

<p>I had 715 coins left on my account, and I have been waiting for a few months until a Zelda item would be released (I knew it would because of Majora&rsquo;s Mask). I check the website nearly daily (I even made a Ruby script to do it automatically) and I knew when the site said it was down for maintenance, some new rewards were being posted. Little did I know at that moment that the site wasn&rsquo;t down for maintenance, it was just receiving so much traffic that it couldn&rsquo;t load (the site seems to be doing just fine today though). After persistent refreshing, I was finally able to log in and claim my reward, the Limited Edition 2014 Platinum Poster Set. My thoughts were between that and the Super Smash Bros v2, but that nice Wind Waker poster settled it. Coins well-spent.</p>

<p>If you have any coins left to spend, now is the time to do it! Any games unregistered, register them now and grab something! Games released now will no longer have Club Nintendo codes in them, so the chance to get more has passed.</p>

<p>P.S. In other related news, the Flipnode Studio 3D download code is supposed to come out later this week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[3D Animation]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/16/3d-animation/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-16T10:58:32-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/16/3d-animation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>3D design and animation is another one of those topics that I&rsquo;ve wanted to learn about for a long time. It is quite a time-consuming activity though, so it was hard to keep up. However, I&rsquo;ve decided I want to take another try at learning 3D modeling and animation. <!-- more --></p>

<p>The great thing about 3D animation is that there is that there are quite a few good choices for software. The bad thing is that many of them are expensive, especially just for learning or using as a hobby.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re a student, one great option is to <a href="http://www.autodesk.com/education/free-software/all">get a free license</a> for some software from Autodesk. This software includes Maya and 3DSMax, which are both industry-standard software for 3D modeling and animation. I am a student, but I didn&rsquo;t take this option due to the limits on the license (expires and non-commercial use only). While I don&rsquo;t plan to make any commercial animations, I just like to have that extra safety net when possible.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-16-2014/blender-logo.png" title="Blender" ></p>

<p>Another great option is to use the open-source Blender. It is completely free and can also be used for commercial use. There are plenty of resources to learn animation with Blender all over Youtube, the Blender docs, and many other places.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-16-2014/simpleman.jpg" title="Simple Man Model" >
A good place to learn Blender is the wikibook, <a href="http://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/Blender_3D:_Noob_to_Pro">Blender 3D: Noob to Pro</a>. I went through a little bit of this about a year ago, but it is very long and requires a lot of reading. However, it is definitely very helpful and covers a lot of material. The models here are ones that I created while going through this book. There were many more, but I didn&rsquo;t get as far in the book as I would have liked. <br>
<img class="noBorder left" src="/images/posts/11-16-2014/house.png" title="House Model" >
<img class="noBorder right" src="/images/posts/11-16-2014/beachball.jpg" title="Beach Ball Model" ></p>

<p><br><br></p>

<p>This time, I&rsquo;m trying out the <a href="http://gryllus.net/Blender/3D.html">Blender 3D Design Course</a> from Neal Hirsig. I find this to be a lot quicker and easier to manage on a time-constricted schedule. So far, the videos are pretty short and the tutorials are very good.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ve already completed the first lesson and will be posting my results of that soon. Hopefully this time, I can keep up with learning 3D animation (thank goodness for weekends).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Smash Bros Amiibo Deal]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/21/super-smash-bros-amiibo-deal/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-21T09:24:12-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/21/super-smash-bros-amiibo-deal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;ve been playing Super Smash Bros. for the 3DS for a little while now, and I enjoy it a lot. I am definitely going to get the Wii U version as well, though I may not play it as much because it isn&rsquo;t portable. If you&rsquo;re planning to get Smash Bros. for the Wii U, you can <a href="http://www.toysrus.com/product/index.jsp?productId=41442366&cp=&parentPage=search" target="_blank">order it from ToysRUs</a> right now and get a free amiibo to go with it! <!-- more --></p>

<p><img class="noBorder left" src="/images/posts/10-21-2014/amiibos.jpg" title="Amiibos" ></p>

<p>This deal is online only. To get the discount, you must add both the Smash Bros. game and the amiibo of your choice to your cart. I think I&rsquo;m going to stick with the Mario amiibo for now, but they have plenty to chose from.</p>

<p>Also, if you have the 3DS version and you&rsquo;re getting the Wii U version, don&rsquo;t forget to register them on Club Nintendo! If you register both versions by 1/13/15, you&rsquo;ll get a <a href="http://club2.nintendo.com/smash-promo/" target="_blank">free soundtrack CD</a> (as well as the Club Nintendo coins and both of the great games).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Student Developer Pack]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/16/free-student-developer-pack/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-16T11:10:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/16/free-student-developer-pack</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The costs of being a college student are tremendous in both time and money. However, there is the occasional perk for students to take advantage of. One such perk for student developers is being offered by GitHub.</p>

<p>GitHub is offering free tools for developers that can prove their student enrollment by providing either a .edu email, school ID, transcript, or any other reasonable proof of affiliation. <!-- more -->The <a href=https://education.github.com>Student Developer Pack</a> comes with many different and very useful resources for a developer. You can get access to the Atom text editor (which is already free), a free Micro account on GitHub with 5 private repositories, a .me domain from namecheap free for one year, a Screenhero account, a student plan from SendGrid (15,000 free emails/month), and a lot more! If you&rsquo;re a game developer, you can also get Unreal Engine 4 for free!</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re a student developer, make sure that you don&rsquo;t miss out on these rare perks. Take these tools and make something cool!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
