<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-17T13:42:20-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club Nintendo Rewards]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/02/03/club-nintendo-rewards/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-03T07:03:02-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/02/03/club-nintendo-rewards</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/2-3-2015/rewards.png" title="Club Nintendo Physical Rewards" >
Nintendo&rsquo;s popular loyalty program will be shutting down later this year to make room for something new (I&rsquo;m excited to find out what it will be like). To help current members spend their unused coins, a bunch of new rewards have been put up on the site, both physical and digital ones. <!-- more --></p>

<p>Yesterday, Club Nintendo put up a good amount of new rewards. Some of the top new physical rewards to grab are Animal Crossing Mini Playing Cards (600), a 3DS XL Pouch: The Legend of Zelda (600), a Super Smash Bros. 3 Poster Set v2 (700), a retro Mario T-shirt (700), a Limited Edition 2013 Platinum Poster Set consisting of Luigi, Zelda Wind Waker, and Pikmin posters (700), the first version of the Super Smash Bros 3 Poster Set (700), a Fierce Deity Link Jigsaw Puzzle (800), and a Legend of Zelda: Majora&rsquo;s Mask 3D Messenger Bag (800).</p>

<p>For Club Nintendo, those are some pretty nice physical rewards to end the program with. But Nintendo also put up a huge offering of digital games as well. The list is huge, so I won&rsquo;t mention them all, but a lot of their greatest games can be bought there. Some examples are Super Metroid, EarthBound, many Mario games, The Wonderful 101, Wii Fit U, some great Zelda games, Super Smash Bros., Kid Icarus, Punch-out, Donkey Kong, and a lot more that are both old and new.</p>

<p>I had 715 coins left on my account, and I have been waiting for a few months until a Zelda item would be released (I knew it would because of Majora&rsquo;s Mask). I check the website nearly daily (I even made a Ruby script to do it automatically) and I knew when the site said it was down for maintenance, some new rewards were being posted. Little did I know at that moment that the site wasn&rsquo;t down for maintenance, it was just receiving so much traffic that it couldn&rsquo;t load (the site seems to be doing just fine today though). After persistent refreshing, I was finally able to log in and claim my reward, the Limited Edition 2014 Platinum Poster Set. My thoughts were between that and the Super Smash Bros v2, but that nice Wind Waker poster settled it. Coins well-spent.</p>

<p>If you have any coins left to spend, now is the time to do it! Any games unregistered, register them now and grab something! Games released now will no longer have Club Nintendo codes in them, so the chance to get more has passed.</p>

<p>P.S. In other related news, the Flipnode Studio 3D download code is supposed to come out later this week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amiibo Craze]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/01/09/amiibo-craze/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-09T10:19:16-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/01/09/amiibo-craze</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/1-9-2015/amiibo.jpg" title="Amiibo Wave 1" >
A few months ago, Nintendo released figures, called amiibo, to be used with some of their popular games using the Wii U&rsquo;s built-in NFC (Near-Field Communication). With a peripheral planned to be released for the 3DS this spring, it will soon be compatible with the figures as well. <!-- more --></p>

<p>These figures can be used in multiple games with more planned for the future as well. Right now, their main use is for training to fight in Super Smash Bros. for Wii U.</p>

<p>Currently, Nintendo has released 18 amiibo in a set of two different waves (12 the first wave and 6 in the second wave). Wave 1 consisted of Mario, Link, Samus, Kirby, Fox, Donkey Kong, Pikachu, Peach, Marth, Yoshi, Villager, and Wii Fit Trainer. Wave 2 had Diddy Kong, Zelda, Luigi, Captain Falcon, Pit, and Little Mac.</p>

<p>I had originally planned to try collecting all of the amiibo, but it seems to be near impossible to do that now without spending more money than I deem it to be worth. Marth, Villager, and Wii Fit Trainer (also known as &ldquo;The Holy Trinity&rdquo;) are the hardest ones to get and together go up past $200 on eBay. I currently have 14 of them (missing Marth, Villager, Wii Fit Trainer, and Little Mac).</p>

<p>It was no surprise that amiibo became highly popular, but I didn&rsquo;t expect the demand to be so high, and I definitely didn&rsquo;t expect the supply to be so low. Virtually every store in the United States is out of stock on Marth, Villager, Wii Fit Trainer, Little Mac, Pit, Captain Falcon, and others that occasionally go in and out of stock. They can be found from foreign sites, but the cost is a little higher, and that isn&rsquo;t very helpful if you&rsquo;re collecting in box as I am (though I do open my favorites if I have a spare).</p>

<p>Nintendo&rsquo;s next wave is set to come out sometime in February, and I&rsquo;ve made sure to preorder all the non-exclusive amiibo (I was too late to grab any of the exclusives). I&rsquo;ve given up my fruitless attempt to collect them all, but I&rsquo;m still going to get as many as I can (at a reasonable price).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Break 3D Models]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/01/05/winter-break-3d-models/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-05T20:27:23-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/01/05/winter-break-3d-models</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So my winter break ended yesterday, and my classes have started up again. I wasn&rsquo;t nearly as productive as I thought I was going to be, but I did create a few 3D models on my own and started on lesson 4 of the tutorials. Each of my models are video game related, and I hope that you recognize them. If not, then I question your taste in video games. <!-- more --></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/1-5-2015/triforce.png" title="The triforce from Legend of Zelda!" >
Here is the glorious triforce from the Legend of Zelda. The style was based off of the version in The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker, when it can be seen at the end of the game. My model may be a little thin, but I think it looks good besides that.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/1-5-2015/pokeball.png" title="A Pokeball from Pokemon!" >
Gotta catch&#8217;em all! A common run-of-the-mill pokeball from Pokemon. This is my favorite of the models I made during the break. It looks just so crisp and beautiful to me, and I really enjoyed making it.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/1-5-2015/rupees.png" title="Some rupees from Legend of Zelda!" >
Rupees! The famous currency of Hyrule in the Zelda games. Who knows what the value of these rupees adds up to?</p>

<p>If you have any ideas about some cool things I should model, let me know! Keep in mind, I haven&rsquo;t passed the simple barrier quite yet though.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shark and Sword 3D Models]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/17/shark-and-sword-3d-models/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-17T10:43:49-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/17/shark-and-sword-3d-models</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just recently finished up lesson 3 of the 3D modeling tutorials I&rsquo;ve been trudging through. With finals this week (and my sudden urge to play a lot more video games), my progress has been a little slow. Hopefully, I can jump up to a much quicker pace when I go home for the winter break this Friday. Lesson 3 had me creating both a shark and a sword as the projects. You can see my work on these in the images below. <!-- more --></p>

<p>Below is my work on the shark model. I think it came out pretty well.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/sharkp1.png" title="The tracing of a shark image" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/sharkp2.png" title="The solid body of the shark before smoothing" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/sharkp3.png" title="The finished shark model without textures" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/shark.png" title="The completely finished shark model" ></p>

<p>Now, my sword model.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/swordp1.png" title="The beginning hilt of the sword" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/swordp2.png" title="The finished model without texture" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-17-2014/sword.png" title="The finished sword model completewith textures" ></p>

<p>I thoroughly enjoyed this lesson and can tell that I&rsquo;m already improving quite a bit. I&rsquo;ve also started working on creating 3D models on my own for objects that I&rsquo;m familiar with. Those will be posted later when I gather up enough of them to warrant a post.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Castle 2.0 3D Model]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/08/castle-2-dot-0-3d-model/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-08T01:10:19-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/08/castle-2-dot-0-3d-model</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So it turns out that the previous model I had done of a castle wasn&rsquo;t the end of lesson 2 as I had originally though. A second optional part of lesson 2 consisted of texturing the castle, so I decided to borrow some time from my sleep and finish the castle up tonight (I may regret that when I have to wake up in a few hours). <!-- more --></p>

<p>I had a few troubles while going through this part of the tutorial. This, I believe, is mostly due to version differences between the most recent version of Blender that I use and the version used to make the tutorials. One problem I had was between cube and flat textures. When the tutorial said to use cube textures, the texture would streak while, according to the tutorial, it would streak in flat mode (which it didn&rsquo;t for me). There were also sizing and other issues that I had to work through, but I ended up with a version that was acceptable for my level of knowledge.</p>

<p>Due to the issues I had, my castle doesn&rsquo;t look quite as good as the castle from the tutorial&hellip;but the ground on mine is textured while the tutorial&rsquo;s isn&rsquo;t (I got my grass texture <a href="http://goodtextures.deviantart.com/art/Green-Grass-Texture-01-155704377">here</a>). Take a look at the images below and see what you think.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-8-2014/castle.png" title="The fully textured castle model" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-8-2014/castle-with-fog.png" title="The finished castle model surrounded by fog" ></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Castle 3D Model]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/06/castle-3d-model/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-06T20:09:43-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/06/castle-3d-model</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I haven&rsquo;t had a lot of time to work on my personal projects lately, and I imagine that I&rsquo;ll have even less time soon with finals coming up. However, I had an extreme urge to create something today, and it&rsquo;s about time I finished up lesson 2 of the Blender tutorials. <!-- more --></p>

<p>This lesson had me building a simple castle. It was, thankfully, a LOT shorter than building the yellow submarine but still very time-consuming. Below are the screenshots of my progress and the final result at the bottom. No animation this time.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress1.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress2.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress3.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress4.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress5.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/12-6-2014/castle.png" title="The finished castle model" ></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yellow Submarine Animation]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/18/yellow-submarine-animation/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-18T19:37:49-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/18/yellow-submarine-animation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, I&rsquo;ve started learning 3D animation using Blender. My first lesson is now complete, and I&rsquo;m excited about continuing through the lessons. The project for the first lesson was to build the famous yellow submarine, as seen on the Beatles album. <!-- more --></p>

<p>I really enjoyed working on this project, but it definitely took quite a bit of time. I took screenshots as I made progress, and I&rsquo;ve posted the finished animation on Youtube. Below are my screenshots, and I&rsquo;ve embedded the completed animation at the bottom.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress1.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress2.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress3.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress4.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress5.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-18-2014/yellow-submarine.png" title="The finished yellow submarine model" ></p>

<p>And here is the finished animation! Sure was a lot of work for just 5 seconds of video.</p>

<div align=center>
<iframe class="noBorder" width="560" height="315" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Gko6Rfti4QY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[3D Animation]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/16/3d-animation/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-16T10:58:32-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/16/3d-animation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>3D design and animation is another one of those topics that I&rsquo;ve wanted to learn about for a long time. It is quite a time-consuming activity though, so it was hard to keep up. However, I&rsquo;ve decided I want to take another try at learning 3D modeling and animation. <!-- more --></p>

<p>The great thing about 3D animation is that there is that there are quite a few good choices for software. The bad thing is that many of them are expensive, especially just for learning or using as a hobby.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re a student, one great option is to <a href="http://www.autodesk.com/education/free-software/all">get a free license</a> for some software from Autodesk. This software includes Maya and 3DSMax, which are both industry-standard software for 3D modeling and animation. I am a student, but I didn&rsquo;t take this option due to the limits on the license (expires and non-commercial use only). While I don&rsquo;t plan to make any commercial animations, I just like to have that extra safety net when possible.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-16-2014/blender-logo.png" title="Blender" ></p>

<p>Another great option is to use the open-source Blender. It is completely free and can also be used for commercial use. There are plenty of resources to learn animation with Blender all over Youtube, the Blender docs, and many other places.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-16-2014/simpleman.jpg" title="Simple Man Model" >
A good place to learn Blender is the wikibook, <a href="http://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/Blender_3D:_Noob_to_Pro">Blender 3D: Noob to Pro</a>. I went through a little bit of this about a year ago, but it is very long and requires a lot of reading. However, it is definitely very helpful and covers a lot of material. The models here are ones that I created while going through this book. There were many more, but I didn&rsquo;t get as far in the book as I would have liked. <br>
<img class="noBorder left" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-16-2014/house.png" title="House Model" >
<img class="noBorder right" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-16-2014/beachball.jpg" title="Beach Ball Model" ></p>

<p><br><br></p>

<p>This time, I&rsquo;m trying out the <a href="http://gryllus.net/Blender/3D.html">Blender 3D Design Course</a> from Neal Hirsig. I find this to be a lot quicker and easier to manage on a time-constricted schedule. So far, the videos are pretty short and the tutorials are very good.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ve already completed the first lesson and will be posting my results of that soon. Hopefully this time, I can keep up with learning 3D animation (thank goodness for weekends).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[November 2014 Nintendo Direct]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/05/november-2014-nintendo-direct/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-05T18:36:55-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/05/november-2014-nintendo-direct</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wow, there sure was a whole lot of good stuff to hear on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KkXmABkDlNE&list=UUGIY_O-8vW4rfX98KlMkvRg">today&rsquo;s Nintendo Direct</a>. If you haven&rsquo;t watched it yet, I highly recommend it. If you just want a basic overview and some thoughts, continue reading. <!-- more --></p>

<p>The very first and most important thing (in my opinion) mentioned in the Nintendo Direct was an official confirmation of a Legend of Zelda Majora&rsquo;s Mask remake for the 3DS! I, as well as many other Zelda fans, have been waiting to hear this news for quite a while now, and I can&rsquo;t wait to play it when it comes out in Spring 2015.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-5-2014/majoras-mask-3d.png" title="Majora's Mask for 3DS" ></p>

<p>Next came Codename: S.T.E.A.M., Nintendo&rsquo;s new turn-based strategy game for the 3DS. I&rsquo;m not generally very interested in turn-based strategy games, but this one did look like it would be a pretty good one.</p>

<p>A little view on Captain Toad: Treasure Tracker followed Codename: S.T.E.A.M. The game looks like it will be a fun game to play while relaxing a little.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/11-5-2014/mario-kart-8-dlc.jpg" title="Mario Kart 8 DLC" >
Nintendo also spent some time talking about the Mario Kart 8 DLC, which will be available on November 13. The DLC pack will include new courses, karts, and drivers from titles such as Legend of Zelda, F-Zero, and ExciteBike. The new characters will be Link, Tanooki Mario and Cat Peach. Another DLC pack is planned for May 2015, and you can get a discount if you get a combo pack of both. The game will also be amiibo compatible.</p>

<p>Speaking of amiibos, they were mentioned often as well. Some games that will be compatible with these figurines will be Mario Kart 8, Kirby and the Rainbow Curse, Hyrule Warriors, Smash Bros. for Wii U, and more to come.</p>

<p>There was a lot more in the Nintendo Direct, including updates on Splatoon, Xenoblade Chronicles X, and Kirby and the Rainbow Curse. Again, I highly recommend you watch it, even after reading this short summary (I didn&rsquo;t cover everything). I see an exciting near future for my Nintendo gaming!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Smash Bros Amiibo Deal]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/21/super-smash-bros-amiibo-deal/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-21T09:24:12-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/21/super-smash-bros-amiibo-deal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;ve been playing Super Smash Bros. for the 3DS for a little while now, and I enjoy it a lot. I am definitely going to get the Wii U version as well, though I may not play it as much because it isn&rsquo;t portable. If you&rsquo;re planning to get Smash Bros. for the Wii U, you can <a href="http://www.toysrus.com/product/index.jsp?productId=41442366&cp=&parentPage=search" target="_blank">order it from ToysRUs</a> right now and get a free amiibo to go with it! <!-- more --></p>

<p><img class="noBorder left" src="http://aradreed.me/images/posts/10-21-2014/amiibos.jpg" title="Amiibos" ></p>

<p>This deal is online only. To get the discount, you must add both the Smash Bros. game and the amiibo of your choice to your cart. I think I&rsquo;m going to stick with the Mario amiibo for now, but they have plenty to chose from.</p>

<p>Also, if you have the 3DS version and you&rsquo;re getting the Wii U version, don&rsquo;t forget to register them on Club Nintendo! If you register both versions by 1/13/15, you&rsquo;ll get a <a href="http://club2.nintendo.com/smash-promo/" target="_blank">free soundtrack CD</a> (as well as the Club Nintendo coins and both of the great games).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Size Squared Promotion for iOS]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/18/size-squared-promotion-for-ios/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-18T10:26:50-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/18/size-squared-promotion-for-ios</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Starting today, I am holding a promotion for my free game, Size Squared, on the Apple App Store! First, the prize: a $15 iTunes gift card code. How do you win? It&rsquo;s simple! <!-- more --></p>

<p>If you don&rsquo;t already have the game, you can download it <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/size-squared/id919713228?mt=8">here</a>. To win the gift card, you must be the first person to achieve AND report at least the listed score for one of the difficulties below. If I happen to be the first person to reach the score, then the person to beat my score is the winner.</p>

<div align=center>
<table width="50%">
    
    <tr>
        <td>Easy</td>
        <td>100</td>
    </tr>
    
    <tr>
        <td>Hard</td>
        <td>150</td>
    </tr>
    
    <tr>
        <td>Harder</td>
        <td>50</td>
    </tr>
    
    <tr>
        <td>Hardest</td>
        <td>30</td>
    </tr>
    
</table>
</div>


<p><br></p>

<p>The Rules:
<br>
    1. Your score must be shown on the leaderboards for that difficulty.
    <br>
    2. You must submit a screenshot of the Game Over screen showing the high score to the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sizesquared">Size Squared Facebook page.</a>
    <br>
    3. The score must be made on an iOS device (iPad, iPhone, or iPod).</p>

<p>Now for some technicalities:
Open only to legal residents of the United States and District of Columbia, who are 13 years of age or older. This promotion begins on Saturday, October 18 and ends on Wednesday, December 31 at 11:59 p.m. Pacific Time or when a winner has been declared, whichever comes first. The sole discretion for declaring a winner lies upon the sponsor. Sponsor reserves the right to cancel or modify the sweepstakes or any portion of it at any time for any reason as determined by Sponsor, in its sole discretion. This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or in association with Facebook, Twitter, or Apple.</p>

<p>Now go play some Size Squared and make some great high scores!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Student Developer Pack]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/16/free-student-developer-pack/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-16T11:10:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/16/free-student-developer-pack</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The costs of being a college student are tremendous in both time and money. However, there is the occasional perk for students to take advantage of. One such perk for student developers is being offered by GitHub.</p>

<p>GitHub is offering free tools for developers that can prove their student enrollment by providing either a .edu email, school ID, transcript, or any other reasonable proof of affiliation. <!-- more -->The <a href=https://education.github.com>Student Developer Pack</a> comes with many different and very useful resources for a developer. You can get access to the Atom text editor (which is already free), a free Micro account on GitHub with 5 private repositories, a .me domain from namecheap free for one year, a Screenhero account, a student plan from SendGrid (15,000 free emails/month), and a lot more! If you&rsquo;re a game developer, you can also get Unreal Engine 4 for free!</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re a student developer, make sure that you don&rsquo;t miss out on these rare perks. Take these tools and make something cool!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to My Site]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/15/welcome-to-my-site/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T11:45:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/15/welcome-to-my-site</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my new website! I&rsquo;m Arad Reed, a current first-year in Computer Science at the University of California - Santa Barbara. Originally from southwest Missouri, I&rsquo;m trying to leave an impression in many places. <!-- more --></p>

<p>I am a passionate programmer and overall tech enthusiast. I&rsquo;ve developed in many different languages and for a variety of platforms. On my <a href="http://aradreed.me/projects/">projects page</a>, you can see some of what I&rsquo;ve worked on. The list includes iOS devices, Android devices, Windows computers, and the Pebble smartwatch. Some of my favorite programming languages include Ruby, C++, and Objective - C.</p>

<p>My most favorite hobby would have to be playing and collecting video games. I generally prefer playing Nintendo games; however, I also play some games for PlayStation. Some of my favorite franchises are Mario, The Legend of Zelda, Uncharted, and God of War. I own many different gaming devices, especially from Nintendo. The NES, SNES, GameCube, Wii, Wii U, many variations of the GameBoy, and the 3DS are just some of the devices I have.</p>

<p>I also used to enjoy solving cubes, such as the Rubik&rsquo;s Cube. I don&rsquo;t do it much anymore, and I&rsquo;ve forgotten a lot about solving the bigger cubes. I went to a competition once, and my official records can be viewed from <a href="https://www.worldcubeassociation.org/results/p.php?i=2012REED01">my page on the World Cube Association</a>. I even made a Windows program that would show the different last layer case of a 2x2 or 3x3 cube and the algorithm to solve it from there.</p>

<p>Again, thanks for reading and visiting my site! Like nearly all projects, it&rsquo;s a constant work in progress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
