<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-15T12:28:24-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to My Site]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/15/welcome-to-my-site/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T11:45:07-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/15/welcome-to-my-site</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my new website! I&rsquo;m Arad Reed, a current first-year in Computer Science at the University of California - Santa Barbara. Originally from southwest Missouri, I&rsquo;m trying to leave an impression in many places.</p>

<p>I am a passionate programmer and overall tech enthusiast. I&rsquo;ve developed in many different languages and for a variety of platforms. On my <a href="http://aradreed.me/projects/">projects page</a>, you can see some of what I&rsquo;ve worked on. The list includes iOS devices, Android devices, Windows computers, and the Pebble smartwatch. Some of my favorite programming languages include Ruby, C++, and Objective - C.</p>

<p>My most favorite hobby would have to be playing and collecting video games. I generally prefer playing Nintendo games; however, I also play some games for PlayStation. Some of my favorite franchises are Mario, The Legend of Zelda, Uncharted, and God of War. I own many different gaming devices, especially from Nintendo. The NES, SNES, GameCube, Wii, Wii U, many variations of the GameBoy, and the 3DS are just some of the devices I have.</p>

<p>I also used to enjoy solving cubes, such as the Rubik&rsquo;s Cube. I don&rsquo;t do it much anymore, and I&rsquo;ve forgotten a lot about solving the bigger cubes. I went to a competition once, and my official records can be viewed from <a href="https://www.worldcubeassociation.org/results/p.php?i=2012REED01">my page on the World Cube Association</a>. I even made a Windows program that would show the different last layer case of a 2x2 or 3x3 cube and the algorithm to solve it from there.</p>

<p>Again, thanks for reading and visiting my site! Like nearly all projects, it&rsquo;s a constant work in progress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
