<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: 3d Modeling | Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/categories/3d-modeling/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-24T11:36:56-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Break 3D Models]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/01/05/winter-break-3d-models/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-05T20:27:23-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2015/01/05/winter-break-3d-models</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So my winter break ended yesterday, and my classes have started up again. I wasn&rsquo;t nearly as productive as I thought I was going to be, but I did create a few 3D models on my own and started on lesson 4 of the tutorials. Each of my models are video game related, and I hope that you recognize them. If not, then I question your taste in video games. <!-- more --></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/1-5-2015/triforce.png" title="The triforce from Legend of Zelda!" >
Here is the glorious triforce from the Legend of Zelda. The style was based off of the version in The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker, when it can be seen at the end of the game. My model may be a little thin, but I think it looks good besides that.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/1-5-2015/pokeball.png" title="A Pokeball from Pokemon!" >
Gotta catch&#8217;em all! A common run-of-the-mill pokeball from Pokemon. This is my favorite of the models I made during the break. It looks just so crisp and beautiful to me, and I really enjoyed making it.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/1-5-2015/rupees.png" title="Some rupees from Legend of Zelda!" >
Rupees! The famous currency of Hyrule in the Zelda games. Who knows what the value of these rupees adds up to?</p>

<p>If you have any ideas about some cool things I should model, let me know! Keep in mind, I haven&rsquo;t passed the simple barrier quite yet though.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shark and Sword 3D Models]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/17/shark-and-sword-3d-models/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-17T10:43:49-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/17/shark-and-sword-3d-models</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just recently finished up lesson 3 of the 3D modeling tutorials I&rsquo;ve been trudging through. With finals this week (and my sudden urge to play a lot more video games), my progress has been a little slow. Hopefully, I can jump up to a much quicker pace when I go home for the winter break this Friday. Lesson 3 had me creating both a shark and a sword as the projects. You can see my work on these in the images below. <!-- more --></p>

<p>Below is my work on the shark model. I think it came out pretty well.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/sharkp1.png" title="The tracing of a shark image" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/sharkp2.png" title="The solid body of the shark before smoothing" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/sharkp3.png" title="The finished shark model without textures" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/shark.png" title="The completely finished shark model" ></p>

<p>Now, my sword model.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/swordp1.png" title="The beginning hilt of the sword" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/swordp2.png" title="The finished model without texture" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-17-2014/sword.png" title="The finished sword model completewith textures" ></p>

<p>I thoroughly enjoyed this lesson and can tell that I&rsquo;m already improving quite a bit. I&rsquo;ve also started working on creating 3D models on my own for objects that I&rsquo;m familiar with. Those will be posted later when I gather up enough of them to warrant a post.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Castle 2.0 3D Model]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/08/castle-2-dot-0-3d-model/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-08T01:10:19-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/08/castle-2-dot-0-3d-model</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So it turns out that the previous model I had done of a castle wasn&rsquo;t the end of lesson 2 as I had originally though. A second optional part of lesson 2 consisted of texturing the castle, so I decided to borrow some time from my sleep and finish the castle up tonight (I may regret that when I have to wake up in a few hours). <!-- more --></p>

<p>I had a few troubles while going through this part of the tutorial. This, I believe, is mostly due to version differences between the most recent version of Blender that I use and the version used to make the tutorials. One problem I had was between cube and flat textures. When the tutorial said to use cube textures, the texture would streak while, according to the tutorial, it would streak in flat mode (which it didn&rsquo;t for me). There were also sizing and other issues that I had to work through, but I ended up with a version that was acceptable for my level of knowledge.</p>

<p>Due to the issues I had, my castle doesn&rsquo;t look quite as good as the castle from the tutorial&hellip;but the ground on mine is textured while the tutorial&rsquo;s isn&rsquo;t (I got my grass texture <a href="http://goodtextures.deviantart.com/art/Green-Grass-Texture-01-155704377">here</a>). Take a look at the images below and see what you think.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-8-2014/castle.png" title="The fully textured castle model" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-8-2014/castle-with-fog.png" title="The finished castle model surrounded by fog" ></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Castle 3D Model]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/06/castle-3d-model/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-06T20:09:43-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/12/06/castle-3d-model</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I haven&rsquo;t had a lot of time to work on my personal projects lately, and I imagine that I&rsquo;ll have even less time soon with finals coming up. However, I had an extreme urge to create something today, and it&rsquo;s about time I finished up lesson 2 of the Blender tutorials. <!-- more --></p>

<p>This lesson had me building a simple castle. It was, thankfully, a LOT shorter than building the yellow submarine but still very time-consuming. Below are the screenshots of my progress and the final result at the bottom. No animation this time.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress1.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress2.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress3.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress4.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-6-2014/progress5.png" title="The castle in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/12-6-2014/castle.png" title="The finished castle model" ></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yellow Submarine Animation]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/18/yellow-submarine-animation/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-18T19:37:49-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/18/yellow-submarine-animation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, I&rsquo;ve started learning 3D animation using Blender. My first lesson is now complete, and I&rsquo;m excited about continuing through the lessons. The project for the first lesson was to build the famous yellow submarine, as seen on the Beatles album. <!-- more --></p>

<p>I really enjoyed working on this project, but it definitely took quite a bit of time. I took screenshots as I made progress, and I&rsquo;ve posted the finished animation on Youtube. Below are my screenshots, and I&rsquo;ve embedded the completed animation at the bottom.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress1.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress2.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress3.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress4.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-18-2014/progress5.png" title="The yellow submarine in progress" ></p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-18-2014/yellow-submarine.png" title="The finished yellow submarine model" ></p>

<p>And here is the finished animation! Sure was a lot of work for just 5 seconds of video.</p>

<div align=center>
<iframe class="noBorder" width="560" height="315" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Gko6Rfti4QY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
