<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Development | Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/categories/development/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-16T15:44:58-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My New Website Launched]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2016/01/16/my-new-website-launched/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-16T15:14:35-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2016/01/16/my-new-website-launched</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, I&rsquo;ve launched my new and redesigned version of my personal website, <a href="http://aradreed.com">aradreed.com</a>. Between going to classes and working on projects, I spent the last week on revamping my website using the front-end framework known as Bootstrap. While it&rsquo;s not quite a masterpiece, I&rsquo;m quite proud of my work. I will still be leaving this domain up separately as my personal blog while my website will host my projects and show off my work. <!-- more --></p>

<p>At first, I wasn&rsquo;t too sure about using Bootstrap for designing my website. It is certainly one of the most popular front-end frameworks on the web, but I didn&rsquo;t know whether it would make my design more complicated or easier. Turns out, it made it a lot easier. Bootstrap had plenty of examples, make customization pretty easy, and is very well-documented. It made my website look a lot cleaner and organized than the previous pages I had up on here. It&rsquo;s not hard to see why it&rsquo;s so popular after using it.</p>

<p>For further information, I&rsquo;m using Namecheap&rsquo;s shared hosting professional package. Normally $78.88 a year, the first year costs only $19.88 (and even cheaper if you find a promo code). I&rsquo;ve owned this domain (aradreed.me) from them for nearly 2 years now and have found them to be a helpful company. After doing some further hosting research, I thought they would be a good fit for my new website as well. Many people and other websites often recommend popular hosts such as GoDaddy, HostGator, DreamHost, and others. A lot of those companies are owned by EIG, a company that&rsquo;s known to buy web hosts and slowly lower their quality and service. GoDaddy, while not owned by EIG, is just the first thing that comes to a non-techie&rsquo;s mind from their mass advertisement.</p>

<p>Anyway, if you haven&rsquo;t already, go check out my new website! I&rsquo;m even working on Unity games to publish for you to play there (currently there&rsquo;s only a local multiplayer version of pong).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Student Developer Pack]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/16/free-student-developer-pack/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-16T11:10:58-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/16/free-student-developer-pack</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The costs of being a college student are tremendous in both time and money. However, there is the occasional perk for students to take advantage of. One such perk for student developers is being offered by GitHub.</p>

<p>GitHub is offering free tools for developers that can prove their student enrollment by providing either a .edu email, school ID, transcript, or any other reasonable proof of affiliation. <!-- more -->The <a href=https://education.github.com>Student Developer Pack</a> comes with many different and very useful resources for a developer. You can get access to the Atom text editor (which is already free), a free Micro account on GitHub with 5 private repositories, a .me domain from namecheap free for one year, a Screenhero account, a student plan from SendGrid (15,000 free emails/month), and a lot more! If you&rsquo;re a game developer, you can also get Unreal Engine 4 for free!</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re a student developer, make sure that you don&rsquo;t miss out on these rare perks. Take these tools and make something cool!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
