<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Nintendo | Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/categories/nintendo/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-05T21:10:49-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[November 2014 Nintendo Direct]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/05/november-2014-nintendo-direct/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-05T18:36:55-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/05/november-2014-nintendo-direct</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wow, there sure was a whole lot of good stuff to hear on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KkXmABkDlNE&list=UUGIY_O-8vW4rfX98KlMkvRg">today&rsquo;s Nintendo Direct</a>. If you haven&rsquo;t watched it yet, I highly recommend it. If you just want a basic overview and some thoughts, continue reading. <!-- more --></p>

<p>The very first and most important thing (in my opinion) mentioned in the Nintendo Direct was an official confirmation of a Legend of Zelda Majora&rsquo;s Mask remake for the 3DS! I, as well as many other Zelda fans, have been waiting to hear this news for quite a while now, and I can&rsquo;t wait to play it when it comes out in Spring 2015.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-5-2014/majoras-mask-3d.png" title="Majora&rsquo;s Mask for 3DS" ></p>

<p>Next came Codename: S.T.E.A.M., Nintendo&rsquo;s new turn-based strategy game for the 3DS. I&rsquo;m not generally very interested in turn-based strategy games, but this one did look like it would be a pretty good one.</p>

<p>A little view on Captain Toad: Treasure Tracker followed Codename: S.T.E.A.M. The game looks like it will be a fun game to play while relaxing a little.</p>

<p><img class="noBorder center" src="/images/posts/11-5-2014/mario-kart-8-dlc.jpg" title="Mario Kart 8 DLC" >
Nintendo also spent some time talking about the Mario Kart 8 DLC, which will be available on November 13. The DLC pack will include new courses, karts, and drivers from titles such as Legend of Zelda, F-Zero, and ExciteBike. The new characters will be Link, Tanooki Mario and Cat Peach. Another DLC pack is planned for May 2015, and you can get a discount if you get a combo pack of both. The game will also be amiibo compatible.</p>

<p>Speaking of amiibos, they were mentioned often as well. Some games that will be compatible with these figurines will be Mario Kart 8, Kirby and the Rainbow Curse, Hyrule Warriors, Smash Bros. for Wii U, and more to come.</p>

<p>There was a lot more in the Nintendo Direct, including updates on Splatoon, Xenoblade Chronicles X, and Kirby and the Rainbow Curse. Again, I highly recommend you watch it, even after reading this short summary (I didn&rsquo;t cover everything). I see an exciting near future for my Nintendo gaming!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Smash Bros Amiibo Deal]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/21/super-smash-bros-amiibo-deal/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-21T09:24:12-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/21/super-smash-bros-amiibo-deal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;ve been playing Super Smash Bros. for the 3DS for a little while now, and I enjoy it a lot. I am definitely going to get the Wii U version as well, though I may not play it as much because it isn&rsquo;t portable. If you&rsquo;re planning to get Smash Bros. for the Wii U, you can <a href="http://www.toysrus.com/product/index.jsp?productId=41442366&cp=&parentPage=search" target="_blank">order it from ToysRUs</a> right now and get a free amiibo to go with it! <!-- more --></p>

<p><img class="noBorder left" src="/images/posts/10-21-2014/amiibos.jpg" title="Amiibos" ></p>

<p>This deal is online only. To get the discount, you must add both the Smash Bros. game and the amiibo of your choice to your cart. I think I&rsquo;m going to stick with the Mario amiibo for now, but they have plenty to chose from.</p>

<p>Also, if you have the 3DS version and you&rsquo;re getting the Wii U version, don&rsquo;t forget to register them on Club Nintendo! If you register both versions by 1/13/15, you&rsquo;ll get a <a href="http://club2.nintendo.com/smash-promo/" target="_blank">free soundtrack CD</a> (as well as the Club Nintendo coins and both of the great games).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
