<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Video | Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/categories/video/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-05T19:25:35-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[November 2014 Nintendo Direct]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/05/november-2014-nintendo-direct/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-05T18:36:55-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/11/05/november-2014-nintendo-direct</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wow, there sure was a whole lot of good stuff to hear on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KkXmABkDlNE&list=UUGIY_O-8vW4rfX98KlMkvRg">today&rsquo;s Nintendo Direct</a>. If you haven&rsquo;t watched it yet, I highly recommend it. If you just want a basic overview and some thoughts, continue reading. <!-- more --></p>

<p>The very first and most important thing (in my opinion) mentioned in the Nintendo Direct was an official confirmation of a Legend of Zelda Majora&rsquo;s Mask remake for the 3DS! I, as well as many other Zelda fans, have been waiting to hear this news for quite a while now, and I can&rsquo;t wait to play it when it comes out in Spring 2015.</p>

<p>Next came Codename: S.T.E.A.M., Nintendo&rsquo;s new turn-based strategy game for the 3DS. I&rsquo;m not generally very interested in turn-based strategy games, but this one did look like it would be a pretty good one.</p>

<p>A little view on Captain Toad: Treasure Tracker followed Codename: S.T.E.A.M. The game looks like it will be a fun game to play while relaxing a little.</p>

<p>Nintendo also spent some time talking about the Mario Kart 8 DLC, which will be available on November 13. The DLC pack will include new courses, karts, and drivers from titles such as Legend of Zelda, F-Zero, and ExciteBike. The new characters will be Link, Tanooki Mario and Cat Peach. Another DLC pack is planned for May 2015, and you can get a discount if you get a combo pack of both. The game will also be amiibo compatible.</p>

<p>Speaking of amiibos, they were mentioned often as well. Some games that will be compatible with these figurines will be Mario Kart 8, Kirby and the Rainbow Curse, Hyrule Warriors, Smash Bros. for Wii U, and more to come.</p>

<p>There was a lot more in the Nintendo Direct, including updates on Splatoon, Xenoblade Chronicles X, and Kirby and the Rainbow Curse. Again, I highly recommend you watch it, even after reading this short summary (I didn&rsquo;t cover everything). I see an exciting near future for my Nintendo gaming!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
