<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Ios | Arad Reed]]></title>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/categories/ios/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aradreed.me/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-18T21:08:27-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://aradreed.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arad Reed]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Size Squared Promotion for iOS]]></title>
    <link href="http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/18/size-squared-promotion-for-ios/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-18T10:26:50-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aradreed.me/blog/2014/10/18/size-squared-promotion-for-ios</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Starting today, I am holding a promotion for my free game, Size Squared, on the Apple App Store! First, the prize: a $15 iTunes gift card code. How do you win? It&rsquo;s simple! <!-- more --></p>

<p>If you don&rsquo;t already have the game, you can download it <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/size-squared/id919713228?mt=8">here</a>. To win the gift card, you must be the first person to achieve AND report at least the listed score for one of the difficulties below. If I happen to be the first person to reach the score, then the person to beat my score is the winner.</p>

<div align=center>
<table width="50%">
    
    <tr>
        <td>Easy</td>
        <td>100</td>
    </tr>
    
    <tr>
        <td>Hard</td>
        <td>150</td>
    </tr>
    
    <tr>
        <td>Harder</td>
        <td>50</td>
    </tr>
    
    <tr>
        <td>Hardest</td>
        <td>30</td>
    </tr>
    
</table>
</div>


<p><br></p>

<p>The Rules:
<br>
    1. Your score must be shown on the leaderboards for that difficulty.
    <br>
    2. You must submit a screenshot of the Game Over screen showing the high score to the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sizesquared">Size Squared Facebook page.</a>
    <br>
    3. The score must be made on an iOS device (iPad, iPhone, or iPod).</p>

<p>Now for some technicalities:
Open only to legal residents of the United States and District of Columbia, who are 13 years of age or older. This promotion begins on Saturday, October 18 and ends on Wednesday, December 31 at 11:59 p.m. Pacific Time or when a winner has been declared, whichever comes first. The sole discretion for declaring a winner lies upon the sponsor. Sponsor reserves the right to cancel or modify the sweepstakes or any portion of it at any time for any reason as determined by Sponsor, in its sole discretion. This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or in association with Facebook, Twitter, or Apple.</p>

<p>Now go play some Size Squared and make some great high scores!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
